All right, faithful. I'm here with John
Lynch, recapping day one of the 2026 NFL
Draft. Now, John, you moved from 27 to
30, and then from 30 to 33. Walk us
through this day one strategy. You know,
what really what we did, we had a list
of guys, okay, if these guys are here at
27, we're turning the card in. They
obviously were gone and found a good
trade partner in the Miami Dolphins,
where we gave them our third, fourth in
exchange for their third, third. So, 138
for 90. So, we we add a valuable pick in
the third round to go back three spots,
and we still have a list of guys that we
really like. We're sitting there at 30,
that list has been unchanged [music]
basically in terms of guys that we
really liked. And so, we talked to the
Jets. We like what they offered. We were
able to add another pick and move back
three spots. And so, now here we are, I
think in a driver's seat, in a cool
position. We [music] get to reconvene as
a staff. Kind of put our thoughts
together, set the day up, come out fresh
and either pick a player or always open
for business to listen for calls. And at
some point, you got to pick players, and
we will. I know trades aren't the most
exciting for for fans when you're going
back, but we're really doing what we
thought was best for our organization,
and I think it's going to put us in in
good position the rest of the draft.
Although a player wasn't drafted to the
49ers tonight, there was still a lot of
action in night one. Tell us what the
energy was like in that draft room.
>> Other than the games we play, it's the
highlight of my year because it really
represents our entire organization
coming together. And I promise you this,
we'll come out a better football team.
And I'm really excited about our
football team as it's currently
constructed, [music]
and it's our charge to make it even
better here in the next couple days.
>> What did the organization gain from
trading that number 27 into additional
draft stock? Well, I think good
positioning and and you know, in terms
of having a coveted pick right there at
33 with players that we still
really like. And so, you know, we
obviously have our eye on some guys,
and we'll prioritize that list. We'll
either pick it or we'll listen. And
but ultimately, we're going to pick some
players, and we're going to make this
team better. All right, John, excited
for the rest of the weekend. Thank you.
>> Thanks a lot.